okay bro time to put your money where
your mouth is and show Robotnik what's
up you really know how to motivate a guy
with his balls my green bro juice sit
there and watch
hey Robotnik do you have a ghost seat I
wouldn't want you to miss the action
don't you dare take your eyes off my
balls
Goddamnit those are some huge [ __ ]
butt cheeks I just want to push him over
and slamming his butt over and over
again with great force jesus [ __ ]
christ holy [ __ ] he look so Goddamn hot
as a spicy burrito from Taco Bell the
way has shirt is unbuttoned oh man I can
barely keep it in my pants he just needs
to bend me over right here and pound my
ass into oblivion
[Music]
that is disgusting look at him over
there stuffing his face with nachos and
cheese dip does he have no manners why
does his hair look like green beans
why is he green anyway while my [ __ ]
blue this place is a complete mess I was
going to buy it but now I'm having
second thoughts well tis that brown
stain over there
you have to be kidding me is that a
[ __ ] poop stain
that's a [ __ ] group stayin
oh wow did you see that Robotnik that
Hedgehog got a strike on his first bowl
we might be in trouble
I am your master who will call me your
roundness cause I am fat and round or
daddy do you understand yes Daddy good
now you ladies see there and watch me
you're about to see the balls of the man
who took over the planet Mobius
you see that I did that on purpose now
the other pins will be easier to hit
watch this
Manic baby why is everybody still
wearing their clothes aren't we going to
play with boss [ __ ] that was cute the
past ten times you said it but not right
now stop with the jokes and get out
there it's your turn and everybody is
waiting
Oh Manic I'm so confused this isn't what
when I say you do something you [ __ ]
do it without question
know your place [ __ ] get up [ __ ] can't
you see my friends and family are over
there stop embarrassing me get up get up
I said get up right now
bro are you sure Mandi is as good as you
think bro I told you already
she's the best there is she told me
so uh how exactly did the conversation
with her go
paym indeed you might if I talk with you
for a minute
you see I'm looking for a replacement on
our bowling team are you good at playing
with balls Manik I play with balls every
night you won't find someone who can't
play with Boyles better than I can
well every night that's awesome you have
to be amazing then you got that right
big boy so who's going to be there
everybody of course we are all going
together everyone well Manica I didn't
know you were into that kind of thing
into it baby I am obsessed with it
you wouldn't believe the kind of things
that go down at the bowling alley
everybody and I mean everybody pulls out
their balls one time even Randy from
down the street was there he is such a
huge fan he couldn't take his eyes off
my balls isn't Randy like three years
old did nobody call the police actually
a police officer just so happened to
drive by while it was going on he
wouldn't stop pushing his balls in
Brandis face our Uncle Chuck ended up
even getting into a fistfight with him
in the front lawn
Uncle Chuck eventually won but the cop
just wouldn't stop grabbing his balls so
we had the gang up on him and started to
smack our own balls in his face I guess
he couldn't handle the stench of my
balls because they had some dried cheese
on them oh when I accidentally dropped
cheese on my balls
they have nacho z-- there at the bowling
alley
bro I [ __ ] up listen Mindy we need to
talk I know my neck I know we were
thinking of different science applause
alright boy this is the final bowl of
the night it's time for you to show me
what you've got
our team is winning by nine points so
all you have to do is knock down one pin
and we win hey chill the [ __ ] out old
man I already told you that I'm the best
[ __ ] around the Sonic
Underground won't know what hit them
when they see how I play with my balls
you can't do this Knuckles you're a
[ __ ] badass but the cool kid no one
can compare it's time to show these
little [ __ ] what happens when you
turn your back on of God
[Laughter]
stop laughing at me I can't do this just
rip his [ __ ] pants bro did we look
that bad when we kicked him off of our
own team are you guys winning very well
okay buddy no place Travis going down Oh
No
somebody stop it somebody stop that ball
stop Apple right now I'll [ __ ] kill
[ __ ] look out there on the scoreboard
do you see it you have won
all right Robotnik you have been beaten
keep your word and released a [ __ ]
father fine take them I don't give a
[ __ ] you won't weigh in the next time
Sonic Underground Knuckles we won
can you believe it we won the game all
thanks to you yet I saw that I'm not
blind you dumped it I guess it really is
a good thing that I suck at bowling
Knuckles I'm sorry I'm so sorry I hope
that you can't forgive me I should have
never kicked you off of a team like I
did it was wrong of me I would like to
ask you to rejoin our team but I can
understand if you don't want to Manik
you chose a large pair of tits over your
best friend do you really think I would
want to join your team
after that I know and I apologized what
more do you want from me KKnux
don't worry I can't stay mad at my best
but forever
mutters mutters mutters
his penis inside makes me bite
[Music]
you the last pure heart beating
my eyes
[Music]
you